//問題文を格納する要素です
const quiz = [
    {
      question: "Nelson Lionet goes abroad on business trips _____ as he works for a foreign trading company.",
      answers: ["likely", "frequently", "reportedly", "widely"],
      correct: "frequently"
    },
    {
      question: "After being transferred to the Atlanta branch, Randy Wilkins started producing _____ successful results.",
      answers: ["selectively", "harshly", "thoughtfully", "immensely"],
      correct: "immensely"
    },
    {
      question: "The new low-cost carrier Northwest Airways is _____ showing a strong presence in the industry.",
      answers: ["well", "quite" ,"yet", "already"],
      correct: "already"
    },
    {
      question: "Due to constraints, Mr.Larson will only _____ explain how to use the app for designing social media campaigns.",
      answers: ["potentially", "briefly", "indefinitely", "distinctly"],
      correct: "briefly"
    },
    {
      question: "After compiling the data, Mr.Roswell's team will be _____ analyzing the results to identify correlations.",
      answers: ["formerly", "agreeably", "fortunately", "thoroughly"],
      correct: "thoroughly"
    },
    {
      question: "_____ everyone can take part in the workshop as long as they are off duty at the time.",
      answers: ["Fairly", "Nearly", "Sturdily", "Suitably"],
      correct: "Nearly"
    },
    {
      question: "All subscribers to Metrin Internet Service Provider _____ receive newsletters from the company.",
      answers: ["economically", "intensively", "periodically", "concisely"],
      correct: "periodically"
    },
    {
      question: "A director at the banquet was surprised at how _____ dressed a few of the attendees were.",
      answers: ["automatically", "shortly", "informally", "persistently"],
      correct: "informally"
    },
    {
      question: "Many tourists visit San Jose to see the _____ built landmark, the DG Tower Bridge.",
      answers: ["amply", "undeniably", "currently", "recently"],
      correct: "recently"
    },
    {
      question: "Since _____ seventy association members are expected to turn out for the luncheon, another table was set up in the dining hall.",
      answers: ["confidentially", "positively", "intentionally", "approximately"],
      correct: "approximately"
    },
    {
      question: "The new accounting software has proven to be more useful than _____ thought.",
      answers: ["initially", "steadily", "specifically", "conveniently"],
      correct: "initially"
    },
    {
      question: "Moore Auto succeeded in advertising their new model _____ to their loyal customers.",
      answers: ["relatively", "effectively", "exactly", "officially"],
      correct: "effectively"
    },
    {
      question: "The CEO announced today in the press conference that the new project is progressing _____ thus far.",
      answers: ["generously", "entirely", "repeatedly", "satisfactorily"],
      correct: "satisfactorily"
    },
    {
      question: "Copies of the purchase orders are filed _____ in the cabinet near the copy machine.",
      answers: ["persuasively", "structurally", "measurably", "numerically"],
      correct: "numerically"
    },
    {
      question: "ETX's sales figures have dropped _____ over the the last three months since CEO Michael Kirk resigned.",
      answers: ["efficiently", "sharply", "diversely", "personally"],
      correct: "sharply"
    },
    {
      question: "All city officials are obliged to adhere _____ to the highest ethical standards.",
      answers: ["strategically", "previously", "strictly", "delicately"],
      correct: "strictly"
    },
    {
      question: "The annual branch managers' meeting is scheduled to be held at the head office at _____ 3:00 P.M. next Wednesday.",
      answers: ["precisely", "exclusively", "extremely", "actually"],
      correct: "precisely"
    }
  ];

